couponproblog.com 2019-03-13

# Privacy Policy – Coupon Pro

**INTRODUCTION**

At Coupon Pro found at CouponProBlog.com (“Website”), we care about you and your privacy is very important to us. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. Our privacy policy provides the latest information about the data we collect and how we use it.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Information You Voluntarily Submit to the Website: We may collect personal information from you such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to the Website by leaving a comment, subscribing to a newsletter, or submitting a contact form.

Information We Collect from Others: We may receive information about you from other sources. You may link your Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, and/or Google accounts to your user profile. If you choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, and/or Google accounts to your user profile, we will receive your name, email address and profile picture associated with that account.

Automatically-Collected Information: We automatically collect certain information about you and the device with which you access the Website. For example, when you use the Website, we will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed the Website. We may also collect information about actions you take when using the Website, such as links clicked.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We may use the information collected in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain the Website.
  * To create and update your account or verify your identity.
  * To enhance the safety and security of our users and services.
  * To communicate with you about our services, marketing, news, and updates.
  * To offer user support.
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries.
  * To send you promotional information, such as newsletters.
  * To host giveaways and contests.
  * To provide personalized content and information, which includes ads or other forms of marketing.
  * To track and measure advertising.
  * To further research and development.
  * To diagnose or fix techonology problems.
  * To address any legal requests.

**COOKIES**

We may log information using cookies, which are small text files stored on your browser by the Website. We may use both session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which stay on your browser until they expire or are deleted.

The Website uses cookies to show you relevant content, improve your experience, and help protect our users. We use cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information, such as pages users access and view, and visitors information to provide you with a more personalized experience on the Website.

**THIRD-PARTY SERVICES**

We do not sell or share your personal information to third parties for third party direct marketing purposes.

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information; however, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the Website to third parties who sponsor giveaways or acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or with law enforcement or in response to legal requests.

From time to time, we may share anonymous data, which does not identify you, with other parties for advertising, analytics, research, and other marketing related purposes. This includes certain information such as cookie data.

**ADVERTISING**

The Website may contain thrid-party advertising and links to third-party websites that are not controlled by the Website. The Website is not responsible for the content of third-party advertising and websites.

We may use display ads, retargeting ads, and may particpate in affiliate marketing.

**PUBLIC INFORMATION  **

We have no control over who reads your posts and comments. Any information you share with a public audience in a public forum, such as the Website, is your choice and the Website holds no responsibility for what others may do with that information.

**CHOICES RELATED TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You may opt out of receiving future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also reach us at [**couponproblog@gmail.com**](mailto:couponproblog@gmail.com) to be removed from our mailing list.

You may also request us to access, amend, and in certain situations erase your person information.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without providing advance notice at any time. If you use our services after an update, you consent to the updated policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**QUESTIONS**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at: [**couponproblog@gmail.com**](mailto:couponproblog@gmail.com)

Last updated: May 24, 2018.
